RG 079:016, Department of Environmental Protection: Natural Resources and Outdoor Recreation
Connecticut State Library
- Series 16. Deputy Commissioner, 1975-2006
  - Susan C. Lavoie, 1995-1998; 2006-007
    - Subject Files
      - Grants (Box 4)
      - Grass Carp (Box 4)
      - Greenways (Box 4)
      - Greenways Assistance Center (Box 4)
      - Greenwich Hunting and Public Safety Committee (Box 4)
      - Griswold Airport (Box 4)
      - Groton Long Point (Box 4)
      - Haddams Meadows State Park (Box 4)
      - Haley Farm State Park (Box 4)
      - Hammonasset State Park (Box 4)
      - Jones (Box 4)
      - Harkness - Friends of (Box 4)
      - Harkness Mansion (Box 4)
      - Harkness Restoration (Box 4)
      - Harkness Incident (Box 4)
      - Harkness Memorial State Park (Box 4)
      - Higganum Cove (Box 4)
      - Hill Top Dairy (Box 4)
      - Home Page (Box 4)
      - Hopemead State Park (Box 4)
      - Hopeville pond State Park (Box 4)
      - Horseguard State Park (Box 4)
      - Housatonic River (Box 4)
      - Housing (Box 4)
      - Human resources (Box 4)
      - Hunting Issues (Box 4)
      - Hunting Public Safety Task Force (Box 4)
      - Indian Affairs (Box 4)
      - Indian Well State Park (Box 4)
      - Information Technology Committee (Box 4)
      - Internship Program (Box 4)
      - IT Resources (Box 4)
      - Jet Ski Event (Box 4)
      - Kojima (Box 4)
      - Kellogg Environmental Center (Box 4)
      - Land Acquisition (Box 5)
      - Land Preservation and Enhancement Program (Box 5)
      - Land Traps (Box 5)
      - Land and Water Conservation Fund (Box 5)
      - Lake Waramaug Boat Launch (Box 5)
      - Lake Waramaug State Park (Box 5)
      - Lattins Cove (Box 5)
      - Law Enforcement (Box 5)
      - Law Enforcement Activity Sheets (Box 5)
      - Law Enforcement Boats (Box 5)
      - Law Enforcement Budget (Box 5)
      - Law Enforcement Critical Incident Response (Box 5)
      - Law Enforcement Marine Equipment (Box 5)
      - Lead Shot (Box 5)
      - Legal Office (Box 5)
      - Legislative Proposals, 1997 (Box 5)
      - Legislative Review (Box 5)
      - Licenses/Permits (Box 5)
      - LifeGuard (Box 5)
      - Lippincott Property (Box 5)
      - Log Cabins (Box 5)
      - Macedonia Brook (Box 5)
      - Management Advisory Council (MAC) (Box 5)
      - Maps and Brochures (Box 5)
      - Maintenance account (Box 5)
      - Marijuna Eradication Program (Box 5)
      - Marine Headquarters-Old Lyme (Box 5)
      - CT Marine Trades Association Fishing Show, 1997 (Box 5)
      - Marine Enterprise Zone (Box 5)
      - Modernization and Improvement Projects (Box 5)
      - David Marnicki (Box 5)
      - Mashamoquet Brook Campground (Box 5)
      - Mason Statue (Box 5)
      - Mattatuck Trail (Box 5)
      - Meigs Point Nature Center (Box 5)
      - Timothy Mellon (Box 5)
      - Mellon Foundation (Box 5)
      - Memos (Box 5)
      - Mercury (Box 5)
      - Mohawk Mountain, 2 folders (Box 5)
      - Mohegan Reservation (Box 5)
      - Mosquito Control (Box 5)
      - Municipal Grants (Box 5)
      - Mute Swans (Box 5)
      - National Heritage Corridor (Box 5)
      - Natural Area Preserves Advisory Committee (Box 5)
      - National Recreation Trails Fund (Box 5)
      - Natural Area Preservation program (Box 5)
      - Natural Resources Council of Connecticut, Inc. (Box 5)
      - Nature Conservancy (Box 5)
      - Naugatuck River Greenway (Box 5)
      - New England Fishery Management Council (Box 5)
      - New England Goals and Indicator Project Briefing Document (Box 5)
      - Nod Brook Wildlife Management (Box 5)
      - Northeast Utilities (Box 5)
      - Northeastern Association of Fish and Wildlife Agencies (Box 5)
      - Norwich Hospital (Box 5)
      - Nuclear Funds (Box 5)
      - Occupational Safety and Health Act (OSHA) (Box 6)
      - Ocean Quest (Box 6)
      - Office of Long Island Sound (OLIS) (Box 6)
      - Office of Long Island Sound Plate Program (Box 6)
      - Office of Urban and Community Ecology (Box 6)
      - Open Space Task Force (Box 6)
      - Organizational Charts BOR/BNR (Box 6)
      - Outdoor-Women Program (Box 6)
      - Pachaug State Forest (Box 6)
      - Paperwork Reduction Task Force (Box 6)
      - Parole Program (Box 6)
      - Peoples State Forest (Box 6)
      - Pequot River Shipworks (Box 6)
      - Performance Assessment and Recognition System (Box 6)
      - Pesticides (Box 6)
      - Pets of Connecticut-Prairie dogs (Box 6)
      - Mike Pochan (Box 6)
      - Pocket parks (Box 6)
      - Pollution Prevention Program (Box 6)
      - Press Releases (Box 6)
      - Project Requests (Box 6)
      - Property Agent 1 Position (Box 6)
      - Putnam Memorial State Park (Box 6)
      - Quarry Head-Wilton, CT (Box 6)
      - Quinebaug Valley Fish Hatchery (Box 6)
      - Quinebaug and Shetucket Rivers National Heritage Corridor (Box 6)
      - Quinnipiac River Restoration (Box 6)
      - Rails to Trails (Box 6)
      - Reginal Center for the Performing Arts (Box 6)
      - Regulations (Box 6)
      - Rental program (Box 6)
      - Reorganization (Box 6)
      - Resumes (Box 6)
      - Ridgelines and Summit Policy (Box 6)
      - Riverfront Recapture (Box 6)
      - River Restoration Grant Program (Box 6)
      - River School (Box 6)
      - River/Watershed Management (Box 6)
      - Rocky Neck State Park (Box 6)
      - Roraback Wildlife Management Area (Box 6)
      - Rose Hill Wildlife MGMT Area (Box 6)
      - Safe Boating Week, 1997 (Box 6)
      - Saugatuck Boat launch (Box 6)
      - Sale-Roraback/Harwington (Box 6)
      - Session Woods (Box 6)
      - Sale-Shepard Hill RD (Box 6)
      - Sale-Statton Brook (Box 6)
      - Clifford Scofield (Box 6)
      - Scup (Box 6)
      - Scantic River State Park (Box 6)
      - Seaark (Box 6)
      - Seafood Task Force (Box 6)
      - Septic Projects (Box 6)
      - Seaside Regional (Box 6)
      - Seasonals (Box 6)
      - Seasonals, 1997 (Box 6)
      - Session Woods Residence (Box 6)
      - George Dudley Seymore Trust Fund (Box 6)
      - Shadbake (Box 6)
      - Shellfish (Box 6)
      - Shenipsit (Box 6)
      - Sherwood Island (Box 6)
      - Shooting Range - Hartland (Box 6)
      - Shortline Ski Club, Inc. (Box 6)
      - Signage (Box 6)
      - Silver lake (Box 6)
      - Silver Sands (Box 6)
      - Sleeping Giant (Box 6)
      - Sleeping Giant State Park (Box 6)
      - Tom Smith - Projects (Box 6)
      - Soapstone Mountain (Box 6)
      - Special Use Liscenses (Box 6)
      - Stage II Vapor Recovery (Box 6)
      - State Ethics Commission (Box 6)
      - State Park Attendance and Revenue (Box 6)
      - State Parks - Budget (Box 6)
      - State Parks Director (Box 6)
      - State Park Fees (Box 6)
      - State Park Film Projects (Box 6)
      - State Parks General Info. (Box 7)
      - State Park Interpretive Program (Box 7)
      - State Park Season Pass (Box 7)
      - State Park and Forest Maps (Box 7)
      - State Park Supervisors (Box 7)
      - State Park Supervisior Association (Box 7)
      - Stewardship land Acquisition (Box 7)
      - Stratton Brook State Park (Box 7)
      - Sugar Maple Trees (Box 7)
      - Summer Music Inc. (Box 7)
      - Surf Chairs (Box 7)
      - Taylor Brook Campground (Box 7)
      - Team Connecticut (Box 7)
      - Teaming with Wildlife (Box 7)
      - Thames Maritime Heritage Park (Box 7)
      - Thames River - Mohegans (Box 7)
      - Tip Program (Box 7)
      - Title V (Box 7)
      - Tobacco shed (Box 7)
      - Topsmead (Box 7)
      - Trash (Box 7)
      - Travel Authorizations (Box 7)
      - Trout (Box 7)
      - T-shirts (Box 7)
      - Tunxis State Forest Shooting Range (Box 7)
      - 2020 Plan (Box 7)
      - Office of Urban and Community Technology (Box 7)
      - United States Geological Survey (Box 7)
      - Urban Revitalization Forestry (Box 7)
      - Voice Mail (Box 7)
      - Vehicles (Box 7)
      - Voluntown (Box 7)
      - Walk Connecticut (Box 7)
      - Waterbury (Box 7)
      - Waterbury Riverfront Greenway (Box 7)
      - Waterbury Waste Treatment Plant (Box 7)
      - Waterfowl Hunting (Box 7)
      - Weber Property (Box 7)
      - Web site (Box 7)
      - Wiersch V. State of Connecticut (Box 7)
      - Western District Headquarters (Box 7)
      - West Rock Ridge (Box 7)
      - Wildlife Division (Box 7)
      - Wildlife Diversity Funding initiative (Box 7)
      - Windsor Locks Canal (Box 7)
      - Windsor Meadow State Park-RV Campground (Box 7)
      - Steve Elkins, Director Bureau of Outdoor Recreation (Box 7)
      - Pam Adams, Director Bureau Outdoor Rec. (Box 7)
      - Chuck Reed, Director Land Acquistion and Management. (Box 7)
      - Ernie Beckwith, Director Fisheries (Box 7)
      - Dick Clifford, Chief Bureau of Outdoor Recreation (Box 7)
      - Ed Parker, Chief Bureau of Natural Resources (Box 7)
      - David Leff, Asst. commissioner Policy and Planning (Box 7)
      - Bud Barone, Director of Law Enforcement (Box 7)
      - Art Rocque, Asst. Commissioner Air, Waste and Water (Box 7)
      - Deans Applefield, Attorney (Box 7)
      - Dale May, Director Wildlife (Box 7)
      - Donald Smith, Director Forestry (Box 7)
      - Bill Evans, Chief Bureau of Financial and support services (Box 7)
      - Unarranged (Box 8)
  - David K. Leff, 2000-2006; 2007-010
    - Documents, 1 computer disc (Box 1)
    - Annual calendars, 2002-2005 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 2002-2006 (Box 1)
    - Speeches (Box 2)
      - Audubon (Box 2)
      - Boating (Box 2)
      - Fisheries (Box 2)
      - Forestry (Box 2)
      - General - Environment (Box 2)
      - Green Circle (Box 2)
      - Introductions, Retirements (Box 2)
      - Invasive Species (Box 2)
      - Law Enforcement (Box 2)
      - Life Guard (Box 2)
      - Long Island Sound (Box 2)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
      - Mosquitoes (Box 2)
      - Open Space, Smart Growth, Sprawl (Box 2)
      - Parks, Greenways, Natural Area Preserve (Box 2)
      - Rivers, Lakes, Park River (Box 2)
      - Wildlife, Hunting (Box 2)
    - Bio/Photo - David K. Leff (Box 2)
    - Eastern Lands & Resource Council (ELRC) (Box 2)
- Series 24. Parks and Recreation, 1975
  - 2003-017
    - "Governor's Task Force Report on State Beaches and Shoreline Parks", 1975 October 16; 2 bound copies and 1 spiral bound copy (Box 1)
  - 2003-033 (part)
    - Hammonassett State Park photographs, undated; 18 photographs mounted on board and 13 loose photographs in unnumbered box (Box Item)
      Some are postcards. Some of the loose items had once been mounted on the board but came off.
      Includes a photograph of Deacon Phineas Meigs' Farm Island House.
- Series 27. Water and Related Resources, 1966-1975; 1988-027 (part)
  - Joseph O. Elmer, Senior Civil Engineer, 1966-1975
    - I. W. R. P. B. (Box 27-1)
    - Encroachment lines (Box 27-1)
    - SCS Program hydrographs and routing (Box 27-1)
    - Joseph O. Elmer log of summer activities (Box 27-1)
    - Loss of valley storage (Box 27-1)
    - Low flow (Box 27-1)
    - Solid waste (Box 27-1)
    - USGS (Box 27-1)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence with private individuals (Box 27-1)
    - SCS correspondence regarding criteria (Duplicates) (Box 27-1)
    - SCS (Box 27-1)
    - Dam consultants (Box 27-1)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence to town (Box 27-1)
    - Meeting notes (Box 27-1)
    - Miscellaneous computations (Box 27-1)
    - Dams - emergency preparations (Box 27-1)
    - Dam regulation: Design (Box 27-1)
    - Soil conservation service (Box 27-1)
    - Erosion and sediment control (Box 27-1)
    - Establishment of new encroachment line (Box 27-1)
    - Encroachment lines (Box 27-1)